var questions = [
	{
		"question":"What is the hardest mineral on display at Killhope?",
		"answer":0,
		"answers":[
			"Quartz",
			"Baryte",
			"Galena"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"Which grey mineral is an ore of lead?",
		"answer":1,
		"answers":[
			"Siderite",
			"Galena",
			"Sphalerite"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"What mineral was predominantly mined at Killhope",
		"answer":0,
		"answers":[
			"Galena",
			"Fluorite",
			"Siderite"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"What is the most common mineral at the Killhope Museum?",
		"answer":1,
		"answers":[
			"Quartz",
			"Fluorite",
			"Smithsonite"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"What is a Spar Box?",
		"answer":0,
		"answers":[
			"A decorative box containing minerals created by miners from the Killhope area",
			"A miner's lunchbox",
			"A box for miners cigarettes"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"Is Killhope still an active mine?",
		"answer":0,
		"answers":[
			"No",
			"It is sometimes used for the extraction of gold",
			"Yes it is still fully active"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"Which mineral is used in the production of toothpaste?",
		"answer":2,
		"answers":[
			"Limonite",
			"Witherite",
			"Fluorite "
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"After what mineral is the property fluorescence named?",
		"answer":1,
		"answers":[
			"Quartz",
			"Fluorite",
			"Smithsonite"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"Whatâ€™s an ore?",
		"answer":1,
		"answers":[
			"A mineral which is grey in colour",
			"A naturally occurring solid material which can be extracted profitably",
			"A small tool used by miners at Killhope"
		]
	},
	{
		"question":"Which mineral at Killhope exhibits the most different colours?",
		"answer":0,
		"answers":[
			"Fluorite",
			"Calcite",
			"Quartz"
		]
	}
];